Hello everyone, this is a video on how to use this website.
So for those who don't know,
this website is where you can upload an audio or video file.
And the website will provide you an SRD file,
which is the format of a subtitle file in return.
And you can upload that file to your editing software and it will do the subtitles automatically for you.
And so first, let us login.
Here you can register an account on our website by this button,
or you can reset your password if you forget it.
But here now we will use Google login first.
And the website will do its job here.
Okay,
so this page is the main transcript page where your uploaded transcript will be listed here.
And if you want to add a transcript,
you click this upload file button.
And you can drag a file or select a file in here.
Okay.
And this place is for you to enter the initial prompt.
And the initial prompt is basically like a sentence of few that describe what the audio
is about and clarifies under the names.
So the transcription AI can do its work better.
So an example of a prompt will be this.
The transcript is about OpenAI,
which makes technology a Dalai GPT-3 and chat GPT with the hope of one day building an ATS system that benefits all of humanity.
And what this prompt does,
it's basically provide the AI the context
of the audio and clarifies under the names like GPT-3,
chat GPT and Dalai,
which would make the transcription more accurate.
Okay.
And this is where you can choose if you want to
translate your subtitles to English.
And let us just submit now.
And before this, before this message shows up,
you can't close your file because it's so upload,
you can't close the browser because it's so uploading.
And after it's done uploading,
your transcript job will be here.
And it's currently running in the background.
So I can leave this page without problems.
And if you want to reach out to us,
if you have any problems,
you want to contact us or
you discover some problems on our website,
please feel free to use this email to reach out to us.
Let's head back to the dashboard page.
Okay, it's done.
It will say it's done successfully.
Refers to see your friends here.
Okay, so this is the view transcript page.
This would be a file name.
And this is the upload time.
And you can play your audio here.
Hey, buddy, how was school?
Everybody?
And here you can see the transcript.
This is a timestamp of each line.
And this is the
titles according to the timestamp.
Okay.
And you have three buttons here.
First, you can copy the transcript through clipboards like without timestamps.
And you can copy
it at any place you want.
And next, you can export the file,
which you click download.
And it would export the SRD file for you.
And last, you can delete this transcript,
which you will just press delete and it'll be deleted.
Yep.
And for those who don't have editing software like Premiere Pro or Final Cut Pro that supports uploading SRD file,
you can go to this website named Clidio.
First, you want to choose your video,
you upload it.
And next, it will allow you to upload a SRD file in there.
Okay.
And it takes a few seconds to run.
That's perfectly normal.
And basically,
we are a transcript,
so you can log out.
You can log in with another account, anything like that.